You're...
Suo Azami?!
You're from Tokyo, ain't you?
What're you doin' in Osaka?
I'm not technically from Tokyo.
What is it about yakuza that makes you
think of everything in terms of turf?
Come on, right, right, right!
Look at me! Right here!
Shit.
You okay, Ozu-kun?
Let's pick up where we left off.
Got plenty to talk about while we drink.
To Be
You
to Marry
I Want
Honest,
Part Three
All right, enough! Give it a rest!
Come on, just a little!
I'm just gonna sew it up some!
I said it's fine! I'll do it myself, later!
But that's too wide for a slit.
What if people see your underwear?
They can't see shit!
Where did you even get
a needle and thread?!
This? From a convenience store, just now.
I bought some ice too, so let's make a
cold compress for your legs and face.
Enough already. Quit nagging.
Unbelievable... How could someone
hit such a beautiful face?
You'd better be over it after
the beating you gave him!
Dude might actually be dead this time.
Wow, you're actin' like a different
guy from when we were drinking before.
So, hi. My name's Somei, not Suzuki.
Somei Yoshino.
You seem to know Kirishima, so you've
probably heard my name before.
Nao-san's not with us, but I'm sure
it'll be fine with just me, right?
Since I seem to be the root cause
of how you were threatening her.
Threatening...?
And you're the cause? What'd you do?
Wait, you don't know?
How much do you really know, Yoshino?
Room 2051 at Grand Residence in Kobe.
That's where you boys have
been workin' out of, right?
Real fancy apartment building.
Big rich kid vibes.
And lemme tell you, it was a
lotta work to figure this out.
Kirishima seems to have known it was in Kobe,
but he was never able to
figure out the location.
But after a three-hour stakeout,
I saw a car with a Tokyo license plate.
Followed that, and it led me to this hotel.
And who got outta that car...
But the punks that Akaza
Shiori had with her.
I dunno what your deal is with them,
but them bein' in Osaka at all points
towards getting back at Kirishima.
So I called him,
and that's how we got here.
That's all I know.
Wait, hang on.
After you called me, how did
you keep him at the hotel?
I just talked to him
and invited him to eat.
Unbelievable.
What kind of saint were you in a past
life to get hit on by Yoshino?
Give it a rest!
You two seem to be confused about something.
I wasn't threatening anyone.
I just knew that Shiota Nao-san and
Miyama-san were in a relationship before.
And since they seemed to be getting
friendly again, I was worried.
That explains it.
I was just hoping we could be friends again,
so the idea of threatening her...
That sounds delusional.
I mean, really, who dates a yakuza's grandson
when you're about to get a job
with a lot of media scrutiny?
I realize how this sounds,
but it's really careless.
Hang on.
We used to date too,
and I was worried, so I wanted
to voice my concerns.
You know, I really am impressed with you.
You manage to walk the line
of doing anything illegal,
and you don't leave any evidence.
I was looking for material
to shake you down with
but couldn't find anything useful.
The thing is, as cautious
as you personally are,
your family isn't quite so careful.
Your parents have spotless records.
Father's a major exec at a big company,
and your mother is a freelance
announcer, right?
With a position as the main newscaster
on a news show starting this fall.
I saw the news on the internet.
And now that you're an adult,
you'll be starting your own career.
From any angle, you're a model family.
That said, this little tryst
was probably poorly timed.
Don't you need to go?
It's fine. I said I was working.
I can't believe you've got a
college-aged son, Sakiko-san.
Come on, don't start...
It's true, though.
Isn't that messed up?
That's your mother, right?
I assure you, the man isn't me.
I did arrange it, though.
Asshole!
What are you mad about?
You use women for the same
purpose all the time.
All I did was arrange the same kind
of encounter for your mother.
So, are we done here?
The punks you brought to Osaka
and the people who asked you
to do this are all gone.
You're the only one left.
You're going to dispose of all the
scandalous material you have on Shiota Nao
and never contact her again.
And after that, I'll consider
what to do with this data.
You really think you've won, don't you?
I can still go to the cops and tell
them that the yakuza threatened me.
People will actually believe me,
unlike scum like you.
I can easily ruin both of your lives!
Pretty sure I can ruin your life, too.
I mean, even if I can't get you busted
for supplying alcohol to a minor,
if I make enough noise about it,
that'd leave some marks on that
perfect record you've got.
What are you talking about?
You asked me to drink with you, remember?
And I refused you, once.
On account of bein' underage.
In other words, you were
supplying a minor with booze.
Underage?! You sure as
hell don't look underage!
Put a sock in it, dickhead!
It says my damn birthday right here!
Besides, you've got the whole premise wrong.
All this nonsense about ruining
someone's life is so stupid...
Knock yourself out.
The only folks that kinda thing works on
are ones who got plenty to lose, like you.
I ain't got a damn thing that
I'm not willin' to part with.
Ruin my life? Give it a shot.
It'll give me a reason to actually end yours.
Well, there you have it.
Are we done here?
How about it? Considering all the
headaches you've given me...
I'm not really that interested
in letting you off so easily,
but agreeing would be the smart move.
Fine.
What's fine?
I'm saying I'll leave the two of you alone.
I hope I never see your shitty face again!
That had better be true.
Because we've got it on the record.
I ain't seen you so beat up in a long time.
What kinda badass were you up against?
No big deal.
Well, you seem fine for the most part...
Did you seriously tail him in that?
It sticks out. A lot.
What do you want me to say?!
A tail in a mini-truck, though...
Look, I was tryin' to leave the
house without anybody noticin',
and this was all I could find!
Sneak sneak sneak sneak...
Tsk.
Did you "tsk" me?!
How come you didn't pick up the phone?
Well... uh... sorry.
I didn't think Kirishima
would drag you into this.
And knowin' you, I figured you'd be fine.
If there's one thing you're
good at, it's fighting.
Didn't expect you to get your ass kicked...
Ih wah a hoke! Juh kihhing!
It was a joke! Just kidding!
So, who was he?
The guy at the karaoke place.
Was he a yakuza?
Three of 'em were trash.
This other dude had a yakuza vibe,
but I don't think he is one.
This Ozu guy's the son of an
Embrace Productions bigwig, right?
Yeah.
That place has had ties with the
Tokusa-kai for a long time.
Whoa, really?
Miyama Kirishima, or I guess technically
the Miyama family, helps them out.
So if this dude was a yakuza, he ain't
affiliated with the Tokusa-kai.
You know more than I figured.
What was he doing in Osaka, though?
Would most people go that far?
I just figured those punks who were
hanging out with the Akaza Enterprises girl
were forcing Ozu to pay out
to get revenge on Kirishima.
Right when I was worried about
my dad getting on my case
about having beef with yakuza,
he reached out to me.
Now I think someone else threatened Ozu
into reluctantly footing the bill.
But what reason could the guy behind this
have for starting trouble in Osaka?
There's gonna be a lot of tedious
internal beef down the line.
How much do you remember
about what you heard?
Could you tell me everything later?
Oh... sure.
Is this really going to help?
I'm not sure it'll matter at all.
Don't worry, though.
I'm sure that Ozu-kun realizes how much
trouble it would be to mess with you any more.
He's not that stupid.
Still, you're best off
staying in the daylight.
If anything, constant exposure
will probably help keep you safe.
That was my plan, anyway.
Is this how you usually operate?
I'm impressed that Yoshino
girl puts up with it.
Y'know, there was something
I wanted to ask you.
What's that?
Well, uh... about Yoshino...
Did she mention me?
I mean, you talked with
her at the school, right?
I was wondering if she
said anything about me.
Like what?
I dunno... like, that I'm a scumbag,
but I'm handsome or something?
Are you kidding me? You're being ridiculous.
She only said that you were acquaintances.
She didn't seem interested at all.
Your chances seem pretty bad.
I see.
Maybe you should give up on her?
I hate to say it, but she seems stupid,
and she has a bad attitude.
I know a few of the girls
you used to be with.
Has your taste in women changed?
Because I don't get it.
She seems stupid, does she?
It's true that you're smart, cute,
considerate, and good in bed.
But for Yoshino's sake,
I'd get into bed with anyone,
even total strangers, not just you.
Did you bait me into hitting you?
You could tell?
We're never going to see each
other again, so don't call me.
I'm going to delete the accounts
I used to contact you soon, anyway,
so I wouldn't worry about it.
You are such a creep.
Oh, hey!
Kirishima—
Independent Taxi
Yoshino.
What are you doing by yourself?
What happened to Toriashi-san?
Well, Shoma came on his bike,
and he couldn't just leave
it around, so I had him go.
I called someone to pick up my ride,
so I'm waiting until they get here.
I see.
How's your leg feel? You wanna sit down?
You're making a big deal outta this.
I'm tellin' you, I'm fine.
I'm sorry, Yoshino.
What for?
A lot, I think?
If anything, I'm impressed you were able to
tweak the timing so it all worked out.
Kinda impressed.
Pull a move like that again, though,
and you're dead meat.
Is that all?
What do you mean?
I thought you'd be angrier.
I mean, I pulled some scummy moves, too...
I'll admit, the mini-truck came as a shock.
Driving that all day must've been tough.
You noticed I was tailing you?
Well, I didn't actually think it was you.
But a mini-truck parked in front
of a hotel so early in the morning
with its engine running
is pretty suspicious.
Not to mention, you don't often
see them with tinted windows.
I mean... it's not like
I wanted to do all that.
But Tsubaki and Shoma both
said to keep an eye on you.
I was in front of that hotel for
five whole hours, y'know?
And when you came out, it was with a girl.
You never disappoint, do you?
And then later, I ran into
her at the college.
I didn't know what was going on,
but I could tell you were up to something,
so I approached her.
That's sharp of you.
More like you're too damn predictable.
What about Ozu Kento?
When'd you find out about him?
When I saw you checking out those
three apartment buildings in Kobe,
I figured something was up.
So Shoma and I reached out
to some real estate folks
and property owners we know.
And wouldn't you know it?
One of the properties had received
complaints about engine noise
and people making a commotion late at night.
They all told me that
someone had rented a room,
and that it was the son of an
Embrace Productions bigwig.
When I looked him up, I saw he went
to the same school as Shiota Nao,
and that they follow each other online.
That's when I knew I was onto something.
It was really exhausting and
took a ton of time, though.
Don't wanna deal with that again.
I never would've guessed you knew
that I was in Kobe yesterday.
I guess I got careless since it was
the first time you'd given me a gift.
You knew?
I had a suspicion.
When you knew where I was, it was
the only thing that came to mind.
It's a tracker used for
infidelity investigations.
Cost about 20-30 thousand yen to rent.
I bought the smallest one
and sewed it inside.
If you knew, why didn't you toss it?
Why would I?
What do you mean, "why"?
Tsubaki told me something.
Whether he's infatuated with
you or actually cares...
You should probably sort that out.
She probably meant for me to come home
to Osaka if you were really dangerous.
The question is whether or
not you actually like me, right?
So I figured, if you really did like me,
you'd hold onto the keychain I gave you.
And I honestly thought you
would get rid of it right away.
But... you seem to really care about me.
That's what I've been saying all along.
I know, but...
Maybe I should've gotten rid of it, though.
When I think about the danger it put you in...
But considering you made
it specially for me...
Then again, yeah. I definitely got careless.
I wonder if this what it's like
to fall for a honey trap?
You're not mad?
I was tracking you with GPS.
You did the same thing to me.
It makes you mad, right?
Not at all.
Then how do you feel?
Figure I oughta start asking
you when I get curious.
You promise not to get mad?
Uh... depends on what you say.
You've got a small head, Yoshino.
My head?
Like I could crush it with one hand.
You want a piece of me?
It's not that.
But sometimes I have these moments...
It's hard to explain...
It's like I want to cherish you,
but sometimes I want to ruin you.
What do you mean?
'Cuz between those two,
I'd really rather you cherish me.
That makes sense. I feel the same way.
Still, I'm glad.
It seemed like you weren't
interested in me at all before.
I wasn't sure what to do.
So, when I realized you were
tracking me, I was so happy!
Even if it's just for my location, it meant
you were interested in what I was doing!
I'd rather you hate me than not care at all
because that gives me much better
odds of us getting together.
Talk about resilient.
Yeah.
So, how exactly do I become your boyfriend?
Remember our bet? We did wrap things up
before midnight, and I'm still alive.
Wait, you didn't think about it at all?
Does that mean I win by default?
Look, I'm thinkin' here!
Rock, paper, scissors!
With the difference in our builds,
I ain't beatin' you in a fight,
and I think you can win any
battle of wits I could come up with.
So we're gonna do this based on luck!
Rock, paper, scissors?
What?!
Oh, nothing. Let's do this.
I got him!
Rock, paper...
I might not look it, but I'm
a pro at rock, paper, scissors!
There's a high chance of
someone throwing rock first!
Which means paper obviously has
the highest chance of winning!
Knowing Kirishima, he probably knows that.
Which means the best move in this case
is to go all the way around and...
Scissors!
Yes! Now I'm Yoshino's boyfriend!
The hell did you throw rock first for?!
That never happens!
You got rocks for brains?!
But I won.
Whoa, hang on... best of three!
Two outta three! Second hand, go!
Okay, first comes rock! Rock, paper, scissors!
Why the hell would you
throw rock a second time?!
Great, now I really am your boyfriend!
So, they're in Osaka?
Got it.
Call Ended